http://www.par.com/privacy-policy

INTRODUCTION
Thank you for visiting www.par.com (the “Site”), which is owned and operated by PaR Systems, LLC, a Delaware corporation (“PaR”). PaR created the Site, so that you could learn more about the products and services that PaR offers. It is intended for informational purposes only. Please carefully review this Privacy Policy Statement and Website Terms of Use (the “Policy”). By using this Site, you agree to be bound by the Website Terms of Use (the “Terms”) set forth below. If you do not accept these Terms, please do not use this Site. If you are dissatisfied with this Policy, please discontinue using the Site. PaR may, in its sole discretion, revise these Terms at any time; therefore, we recommend you visit this page periodically to review the Terms.
Although PaR strives to provide useful and timely information on the Site, PaR makes no representations, warranties or assurances as to availability, accuracy, currency or completeness of this Site or its contents. PaR shall not be liable for any damages or injury resulting from your access to, inability to access, or use of this Site, including, without limitation, any damages or injury arising from any links to other sites contained within or referred to in this Site.
YOUR PRIVACY IS IMPORTANT TO PAR
PaR Systems, LLC (PaR) is committed to respecting an individuals privacy. While PaR had developed this policy with the intent of meeting the European Union General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) we are committed to meeting the same standards across the global organization.
PaR complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. PaR has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/.
PaR and all of its subsidiaries adhere to the Privacy Shield. PaR collects information about employees that are required to support payroll, benefits, background checks, and personnel matters related to performance. PaR does not sell or release any personal data to third parties other than those it uses in the process of supporting outsourced operations. Individuals have the right to access their personal data and should contact the Privacy Officer if they have concerns about the data that is collected or would like to limit it any way. Most, if not all, data collected is required in order to be employed by PaR or in the process of doing business with PaR.In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, PaR commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. Individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact PaR at:
PaR Systems, LLCAttn: Data Privacy Officer707 County Road E WestShoreview, Minnesota 55126-7007 (USA)Phone: (800) 464-1320Email: privacy@par.com
PaR commits to cooperate with the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and comply with the advice given by the panel with regard to personal data transferred from the EU. The Federal Trade Commission has jurisdiction over PaR's compliance with the Privacy Shield.
Individuals have the possibility, under certain conditions, to invoke binding arbitration for complaints regarding Privacy Shield compliance not resolved by any of the other Privacy Shield mechanisms. See Annex I for additional information: https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction.
PaR has a legal requirement to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including meeting national security or law enforcement requirements. In the context of an onward transfer, PaR is responsible for the processing of personal information it receives under the Privacy Shield and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. PaR uses third parties to support background checks, payroll and benefits.
PaR does not collect identifying information about you, unless you voluntarily submit that information. Please do not provide to PaR any confidential information about you or anyone else via electronic communication, except for employment purposes. Because PaR does not invite or solicit such confidential information, PaR cannot assure that any information that you provide to PaR will be kept confidential, except for information that is requested and submitted for compliance with our Affirmative Action Programs. Employment information is kept confidential.
The only way to become a customer of PaR is by entering into an express written agreement with PaR. Sending PaR an e-mail message will not make you a customer of PaR. The contact information for each of PaR's offices is included in the "Contact Us" page of this Site.
USE AND DISTRIBUTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IS LIMITED
Any personal information that you submit to PaR via the "Contact Us" or "Employment Opportunities" pages will only be used within PaR's domain. No personal information collected by PaR via the Site will be sold, traded, rented or otherwise disclosed to third parties provided, however, PaR reserves the right to disclose any information in its possession if it is required to do so by law, or if PaR reasonably determines that such disclosure is necessary to comply with applicable law, or to defend PaR's rights or property, or to respond to an emergency situation.
CONTACT US
PaR's "Contact Us" page is the primary means of communication between PaR staff and Site visitors. Site visitors may use the "Contact Us" page to submit inquiries regarding PaR, the Site or its contents; information related to the Site visitors' primary areas of interest; notifications regarding broken links; concerns regarding privacy; and/or praise or complaints related to PaR and/or the Site. Site visitors should use the "Employment Opportunities" page to submit information related to employment requests, including resumes. All information that is forwarded to PaR via the "Contact Us" or "Employment Opportunities" pages will be directed only to the appropriate PaR personnel. The only way such information will be collected is if you submit such information into an open text field or on the "Employment Opportunities" page, or contact us by e-mail.
PAR COLLECTS NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION
PaR collects non-personal information about your use of the Site through the use of a standard technology referred to as "cookies." Cookies are small text files that are installed on your computer's hard drive during your visit that allow PaR to recognize you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies allow PaR to monitor the number of people using the Site, to determine which aspects of the Site are most popular among visitors, to determine the length of time visitors access the Site, and to develop methods for improving the Site. PaR does not use cookies to collect or store personal information about you. Most browsers offer instructions on how to reset the browser to reject cookies in the "Help" section of the toolbar. You do not have to accept our cookies to use the Site.
PaR also may automatically collect certain non-personal information about you, such as the domain name from which you access the Internet, the IP address of the computer you are using, the Internet address from which you linked directly to the Site, or the type of browser or computer operating system you use. Any non-personal information that is automatically collected by PaR will be maintained indefinitely by PaR and used for PaR's internal business and marketing purposes, such as assessing Site usage and traffic patterns.
LINKS
PaR may include links to other websites that permit you to leave the Site. PaR does not own, control or operate such links or their websites, except for links and corresponding websites of business acquisitions, and PaR is not responsible for the contents of any other such linked website or any link contained in another linked website. The inclusion of any such link does not imply endorsement of the website, or any product or service. The use and/or privacy provided by the operator of a linked website as to any information you provide in accessing a linked website is in no way subject to this Policy. Each linked website may have its own policies that could differ considerably from this Policy, or the linked website may not display any privacy policy at all. In any event, even though a linked website may be accessed through the Site, PaR cannot be responsible for any use that a linked website may make of your information.
SECURITY PROCEDURES
PaR operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall password protection systems. PaR's security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced, as necessary, and only authorized individuals have access to the information you provide. Although we make every reasonable effort to protect the information you provide, we cannot guarantee the security of systems that are connected to the Internet or the security of information transmitted over the Internet.
WARRANTY DISCLAIMER
PAR, ITS SUBSIDIARIES, AND THEIR RESPECTIVE DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, REPRESENTATIVES, SUPPLIERS, AND CONTRACTORS (ALL OF THE FOREGOING, COLLECTIVELY, THE "REPRESENTATIVES") MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES WITH RESPECT TO THIS SITE, ITS CONTENT OR ABOUT THE SUITABILITY OF THE INFORMATION CONTAINED ON THE SITE FOR ANY PURPOSE. ALL SUCH MATERIALS ARE PROVIDED "AS IS," WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. PAR AND ITS REPRESENTATIVES HEREBY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, IMPLIED WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT WITH RESPECT TO THIS SITE AND ANY WEBSITE WITH WHICH IT IS LINKED. PAR ALSO MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES AS TO WHETHER THE INFORMATION ACCESSIBLE VIA THIS SITE, OR ANY WEBSITE WITH WHICH IT IS LINKED, IS ACCURATE, COMPLETE OR CURRENT. IT IS YOUR RESPONSIBILITY TO EVALUATE THE ACCURACY AND COMPLETENESS OF ALL INFORMATION, OPINIONS AND OTHER MATERIAL ON THIS WEBSITE OR ANY WEBSITE WITH WHICH IT IS LINKED. PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT AND WEBSITE TERMS OF USE
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IN NO EVENT SHALL PAR AND/OR ITS REPRESENTATIVES BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, LOSS OF USE, LOSS OF DATA, LOSS CAUSED BY A COMPUTER OR ELECTRONIC VIRUS, LOSS OF INCOME OR PROFIT, LOSS OF OR DAMAGE TO PROPERTY, CLAIMS OF THIRD PARTIES, OR OTHER LOSSES OF ANY KIND OR CHARACTER ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH THE USE OF THIS SITE OR ANY WEBSITE WITH WHICH IT IS LINKED, OR FOR ANY INFORMATION OBTAINED THROUGH THIS SITE, WHETHER BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF PAR OR ANY OF ITS REPRESENTATIVES HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. YOU ASSUME TOTAL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ESTABLISHING SUCH PROCEDURES FOR DATA BACK-UP AND VIRUS CHECKING AS YOU CONSIDER NECESSARY.
NO UNLAWFUL OR PROHIBITED USE
You may view, download and print material from this Site for your own use only, provided that you do not remove any trademark, copyright, or other notice contained in such materials. You agree not to otherwise copy, modify, distribute, reuse, resell, license, create derivative works from, or otherwise transfer materials from this Site, without the express written permission of PaR.
All links to this Site must appear as hypertext, without use of PaR’s logos or trademarks. Do not use a hyperlink to present materials on this Site as your own. Deep-linking is strictly prohibited unless approved by PaR in writing (a deep-link is a hyperlink that bypasses a website’s home page and brings a visitor directly to an interior page). Do not frame this Site or any content provided by PaR (framing is an alternative form of linking that allows viewing of a linked web page within a “frame” of the original website). Do not use PaR’s URL’s, trademarks, meta tags, or other materials in the meta or alt tags of any other website (such tags provide information about a website which search engines use to prioritize results), or to effect any “matchmaking” advertising by third parties.
You agree that you will not use this Site for any purpose that is unlawful, or prohibited by the Terms of this Policy. You may not use the materials contained on this Site in a manner that suggests any association with or endorsement of any product or service, or which violates any property, privacy or other rights.
INDEMNIFICATION
You agree to defend, indemnify, and hold harmless PaR and its Representatives from and against any claims, actions or demands, including without limitation, reasonable legal and accounting fees, alleging or resulting from (i) any content or other material You submit to the Site, (ii) your use of the Site or its contents, or (iii) your breach of the terms of these Terms. PaR will provide notice to you promptly of any such claim, suit, or proceeding.
GENERAL
PaR makes no claims that the Site or its contents may be lawfully viewed or accessed outside of the United States. Access to the Site or its contents may not be legal by certain persons or in certain countries. If you access the Site from outside of the United States, you do so at your own risk and are responsible for compliance with the laws of your jurisdiction. These Terms are governed by the internal substantive laws of the State of Minnesota, without respect to its conflict of laws principles. Jurisdiction for any claims arising under this agreement shall lie exclusively with the state or federal courts within the State of Minnesota. If any provision of these Terms is found to be invalid by any court having competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of these Terms, which shall remain in full force and effect. No waiver of any term of these Terms shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or any other term. In addition, PaR’s failure to enforce any term of these Terms shall not be deemed as a waiver of such term or otherwise affect PaR’s ability to enforce such term at any point in the future. Except as expressly provided in an additional agreement or software license or material on particular Site pages, these Terms PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT AND WEBSITE TERMS OF USE Page 4
constitute the entire agreement between you and PaR with respect to the use of the Site. No changes to these Terms shall be made except by a revised posting on this page.
TERM AND TERMINATION
These Terms will remain in full force and effect while you are a user of the Site at any level. PaR reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to pursue all of its legal remedies, including but not limited to, removal of your information from the Site and immediate termination of your registration with or ability to access the Site, upon any breach by you of these Terms. Even after you are no longer a user of the Site, certain provisions of these Terms will remain in effect.
THESE TERMS CONSTITUTE A BINDING AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU AND PAR, AND ARE ACCEPTED BY YOU UPON YOUR USE OF THE SITE.
Date of Last Update to Policy: October 2019
Back To Top
